<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>helpful information about art supplies on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>/articles/</link>
    <description>Recent content in helpful information about art supplies on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/articles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>All about Erasers - part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/_articles/all-about-erasers-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/_articles/all-about-erasers-1/</guid>
      <description>The eraser may seem like the most straightforward tool at an artist’s disposal: erasers remove marks and lines, simple as that. But, in fact there are a number of different types of erasers designed for different purposes and different materials.
Pink erasers are fairly stiff, solid and sometimes come on the ends of pencils. They were once made out of pink colored rubber. Now they&amp;rsquo;re usually mixtures of rubber and synthetic plastics, and they&amp;rsquo;re not always pink.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All about Erasers - part 2</title>
      <link>/articles/_articles/all-about-erasers-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/_articles/all-about-erasers-2/</guid>
      <description>Gum erasers (also called &amp;lsquo;art-gum erasers&amp;rsquo;), like pink and white erasers, are good for clearing large areas of a page. Gum erasers are not as stiff as pink erasers and are preferable for thin papers like drafting vellum or newsprint. Because they are made from a softer, coarser type of rubber, gum erasers are often a bit crumbly (especially if old and dried out). This isn’t an especially bad thing since it’s the little crumbles, called &amp;lsquo;eraser dust&amp;rsquo;, that actually hold the graphite lifted out of the page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Choosing a Sketchbook - part 1</title>
      <link>/articles/_articles/choosing-a-sketchbook-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/articles/_articles/choosing-a-sketchbook-part-1/</guid>
      <description>For artists, sketchbooks are essential. They provide an easy place to record ideas, make studies, and experiment with new techniques. Sometimes sketchbooks themselves are treated as finished pieces of art. Typically, however, sketchbooks are personal journals or archives that artists can refer back to in order to remind themselves of ideas or keep a record of their progress. Since sketchbooks need to stand the test of time, they need to be sturdy, conveniently sized and suitable to the type of media that an artist uses.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>